<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Note on Anti-Suicide Project</title>
    <link>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Note on Anti-Suicide Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 03:47:27 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1) Introduction</title>
      <link>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/1.-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 03:47:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/1.-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Hoi, my name is Pixel, and I spent a long time creating this because I care about you and I don&amp;rsquo;t want you to end your life. You are important. When reading this, I want you to imagine I&amp;rsquo;m there saying it to you in person. This was created by someone who can relate. Due to my disabilities, my emotions are stronger than most other people’s. I have been through this since I was eight, and I am still here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2) Im Valueless</title>
      <link>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/2.-im-valueless/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 03:47:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/2.-im-valueless/</guid>
      <description>One common reason you might want to end your life is you feel you have no value. If you’re like that, I have a few points I wanna make. Every person is made in the image of God, who is divine; and therefore everyone has value. Even Hitler had value: he excelled in the area of leadership. Everyone has gifts, (that includes you,) and there is a lot of value in that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3) Meaningless and Suffering</title>
      <link>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/3.-life-is-meaningless-or-suffering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 19:59:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/3.-life-is-meaningless-or-suffering/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Life Is Meaningless and Suffering&amp;rdquo;
You might say your life is too hard. Hard to a point that you want it to end. The thing is, we were made to adapt and become stronger through suffering, pain and trials. It builds character. In books, movies and video games the characters have to struggle. If they don&amp;rsquo;t it&amp;rsquo;s bland and pointless. The best stories have the character overcome the greatest obstacles. If you only had a good and easy life you wouldn’t realize it was good because you never experienced bad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4) No One Cares</title>
      <link>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/4.-no-one-cares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 19:59:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/4.-no-one-cares/</guid>
      <description>I already touched a bit on this in the beginning where I explained how more people care then you understand. But I have more to say about it. A big reason I find people saying no one cares is because they are hanging with the wrong crowd: people who use you and don&amp;rsquo;t care. Now if you’re wanting a group of great people, I would suggest a youth group/ young adult group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5) Mental Illness</title>
      <link>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/5.-mental-illness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 19:59:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/5.-mental-illness/</guid>
      <description>Some people actually have chemical imbalances in the brain that causes them to always feel depressed or even suicidal. This can often be treated with medications like antidepressants. When people try antidepressants people sometimes take months to find the ones that work, even ten attempts or more, but in the end they feel happy and better, so wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be worth it? If you&amp;rsquo;re feeling suicidal and depressed all the time, I would suggest seeing a doctor and telling them how long it&amp;rsquo;s been lasting, especially if it&amp;rsquo;s been 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6) Final Points</title>
      <link>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/6.-final-points/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 19:59:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pixelbyte21.github.io/AntiSuicideProject/the-note/6.-final-points/</guid>
      <description>A prison guard in Edmonton once said “you can always commit suicide tomorrow”. Kind of a weird statement at first, but it&amp;rsquo;s true. In our society people always procrastinate about everything. &amp;ldquo;I will mow the lawn tomorrow&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Only five more minutes of this game before bed&amp;rdquo;. Why not procrastinate about this too? You can always just push it till tomorrow. So just do that. And do it some more. And do it till you can&amp;rsquo;t do it anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>